One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Show Yourselves, Straw Hat Pirates!
The Crew's Hopeless Counterattack!
Hey! What's wrong, Cindry-chan?!
My body...
Won't move.
Tears came out...
Involuntarily.
Your body won't move?!
What the hell are you talking about?!
Stop that false crying already!
Who do you think you have to thank for moving as if you had a soul?!
You zombies only exist to obey your master's orders!
It's as if the owner of the body is fighting back...
Even though she died ten years ago...
Does a body without a soul have feelings...?
Probably...
Even if we investigated all the libraries in the world, we wouldn't find an answer.
I'll kill... you both...
That's it!
You've finally come to your senses, Cindry-chan!
Be sure to distract them until I'm out of here!
It's a shame...
Here I thought I was witness to a miracle...
Doce Fleur!
Twelve Flowers
Wait!
W-What's with this shaking?!
Damn it!
You stupid pirate-deer! Acting like a person and siding with the dead!
You're not even human!
You stupid monster!
Our captain...
Doesn't care whether you're a monster, a cyborg, a pervert, a long-nose, or a moss head...
He can make anyone follow him!
Unlike you, who makes use of mindless corpses for your own schemes!
Let go of me, bastard!
Robin!
Alright, leave it to me!
Pierna Fleur!
Leg Flower
Huh? What?!
W-Wait a minute, Dr. Chopper!
If you smash my head from such a high place...
The brain of the world's greatest genius would be destroyed!
Is that what you want?!
I'm fine with that.
Your head is more rotten than those zombies of yours!
Take this!
Robi-Cho Suplex!
Nearby, in the Special Freezer Room
It's much bigger than a giant.
So this is my zombie.
I've been expecting you, Oars!
The body and shadow have merged at last!
Are you a fully obedient zombie now?
Answer! Who is your master?
My Master is Moriah-sama.
What?!
Hey, what're you saying?!
Are you really my shadow?!
Don't listen to him!
Who're you, straw hat guy?
Then, I shall give you your first order.
They are currently rampaging throughout every corner of Thriller Bark.
Those are the Straw Hat Pirates.
Pulverize them without mercy, and send them back to their ship.
Whether they live or die, I don't care!
A little violence won't kill those over 100 million anyway.
Don't hold back!
Give them a taste of your power!
Yes, Moriah-sama.
Ah! Found you, Straw Hat.
See you later, Straw Hat!
You're not getting away!
Rubber...
W-W-Wait a minute!
That's dangerous!
Bell!
What?!
Luffy's zombie!
Oars!
The floor is crumbling!
Chopper, this way!
That was close.
So this is...
Luffy?
Both Hogback and Cindry fell to the floor below us.
Damn!
Too heavy!
Cindry-chan, move this rock...
C-Cindry-chan, quickly!
Hurry up and help me!
Look, Oars is coming!
I...
I, the great genius...
I'm gonna get squished!
Hey, why're you just standing there?!
I'm your master!
My body...
won't move.
What?!
Again with that ridiculous nonsense!
You zombies only exist to be loyal!
Quickly, help me!
You're nothing but a pretty face!
You worthless corpse!
Hey! Hurry up, Cindry!
Oars is here!
Oars, look down, you fool!
It's me, you ungrateful idiot!
I'm the one who fixed your body so you could move again!
Nearby, in the corridor outside Perona's room
W-W-Wait a minute!
W-What's going on?!
These tremors are completely different!
Lu-Lu-Lu...!
Luffy's zombie!
Nearby, in the church
Hey, hey, hey, hey! What's with this shaking?!
No way!
Luffy's zombie?!
Damn!
Nami-san, this isn't the time to be sleeping!
It can't be helped...
We need to escape.
Nami-san?
Nami-san disappeared.
Don't tell me...!
The tables have turned...
Bastard!
You're still conscious?!
You beast-man, show yourself!
It seems this demon has finally become our servant!
Checkmate!
This time the bride is mine!
Damn it!
Give back Nami-san!
Where are you hiding?!
I hope you have fun with the ultimate zombie!
Something came out!
T-That's...
A zombie!
It's Luffy's zombie.
Look over there!
The one who came out...!
Isn't that the curly cook?!
Damn!
Nami-san!
What is that stupid cook doing in there?!
Wait!
Moriah!
So you'd rather keep chasing me?
That huge copy bothers me, but...
If I want to recover everyone's shadows, I gotta beat the hell out of Moriah!
You're not getting away!
The Church
Look!
It is I who has the last laugh!
You seem to be deep asleep still...
I'll find us a new place...
And we shall have our wedding once again.
My silent bride.
Is Perona-sama okay?!
She has lost consciousness.
It seems she's not injured.
Commander Kumashi and the Vice-Commander are both wiped out.
That long-nose bastard!
Let's get her outta here.
This mansion is so damn dangerous!
The special zombie will take revenge for us!
Get away from the mansion!
The special zombie is fighting!
He's so damn huge!
I can see his head towering over the mansion!
Perona's Wonder Garden
Usopp!
Chopper!
Robin!
W-W-We're in trouble!
A-A-Attached to Luffy's zombie's arm are...!
O-O-Our...!
Wanted posters!
He is...
Definitely after us!
Show yourselves!
Straw Hat Pirates!
That bastard...!
Now he's getting in our way!
That Luffy!
Does he really intend to destroy his own crew?!
He was surely ordered to.
I wonder if the real Luffy is alright...
What is that thing?!
Can we really beat such a monster?!
Interesting.
Wait, Moriah!
A dead end.
While you're here, all of your crewmates are becoming victims of your own power, Straw Hat!
What is that?!
Such a scary face!
That's...
Hey! Usopp! Is that you over there?!
Zoro!
What are you doing on the roof?!
Franky, Brook, you two are alright!
Hey! Step aside!
Why're you getting in our way, Luffy?
Luffy...?
He is... my enemy.
My name is Oars.
Pleased to meet you!
He is provoking that monster.
That stupid cook...
Did he manage to save Nami at least?
Shouldn't you be more worried about yourself than the girl right now?
This is bad!
Sanji's in danger!
This is unexpected.
I thought they were merely after our shadows.
Maybe we caused a little too much trouble.
It seems they were only after Luffy's shadow.
Scary.
So scary!
We can't win against such a monster!
Your face resembles the one in this poster.
You're one of the pirates.
Rubber...
Luffy's technique!
Is he going to stretch?!
Is he also a rubberman?!
Scythe!
He didn't stretch, but...!
With that range and destructive power, there's no need!
Oars...
I've heard that name before...
Is he the demon Oars, the legendary "Nation Snatcher"?
Collier Frit!
Fried Neck
Sanji!
So huge, yet so fast.
This is bad!
He'll die!
Hey! Stop!
Sanji!
Disappear, little pirate!
Firebird Star!
Sanji!
He's heading over here!
This is bad!
Franky, lure him over here!
Got it!
Take this, monster!
Watch out!
You two, head to the lower roof!
One Gorilla.
Two Gorilla!
Three Swords Style....
Two-Gorilla Beheading!
Rubber...
Volcano!
Zoro! Are you okay?!
He'll die if he falls from such a height!
Take this, monster!
Weapons Left!
What incredible agility!
He avoided it again!
Franky!
Brook!
Zoro's coming down!
Cien Fleur!
One Hundred Flowers
Spider Net!
Damn!
Take this!
You're a zombie too!
Deadly... Salt Star!
It... It's not enough for that huge body!
Heavy Gong!
D-Damn you...
Luffy...
I don't know you guys.
I am Moriah-sama's servant...
Oars!
Translation & initial syncing, Vegapunk Fansubs
Syncing, Galaxy 9000, , Sync-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Feeso
Video editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, Halee
Raw provider, SOFCJ-Raws